1. The two elderly Texas millionaires were impressed by the sophisticated electronic
eavesdropping equipment.
2. The two elderly Texas millionaires were impressed by the sophisticated electronic
3. At the moment, the two elderly Texas millionaires are being impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
4. The two elderly Texas millionaires will be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment.
5. The two elderly Texas millionaires would be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment if there were more practical applications for
it.
6. The two elderly Texas millionaires that had been impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment if there had been more practical applications
for it.
7. The two elderly Texas millionaires that have been so impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment are now researching a new
program.
8. The two elderly Texas millionaires have been impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment for a long time now.
9. The two elderly Texas millionaires had been impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment long before the burglary was thwarted.
10. The two elderly Texas millionaires will have been thoroughly impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment by the time I've done my
The two elderly Texas millionaires ought to be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic
eavesdropping equipment. Twelve, the two elderly millionaires should be impressed
by the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
Thirteen, the two elderly Texas millionaires shouldn't be too impressed by
the sophisticated sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
14. The two elderly Texas millionaires should have been impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
15. Given the circumstances, the two elderly Texas millionaires shouldn't have
been that impressed by the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
16. We think that the two elderly Texas millionaires could easily be impressed by
the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
17. No matter what we did, the two elderly Texas millionaires couldn't be impressed
by even the most sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
18. Two elderly Texas millionaires could have been impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment, but we're not sure.
19. The two elderly Texas millionaires couldn't have been impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment because they left after five
minutes.
20. The two elderly Texas millionaires might be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic electronic eavesdropping equipment this time around.
21. The two elderly Texas millionaires might have been impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment, but they gave no indication one
way or the other.
22. The two elderly Texas millionaires must be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they're considering a huge order.
23. The two elderly Texas millionaires must have been impressed by the
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment because they ordered so much of
it.
24. The two elderly Texas millionaires can be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they don't know much about
25.
The two elderly Texas millionaires can't be impressed by the sophisticated
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they invented most of the state-of-the-art
technology currently available.